Herold J. Wiens Collection
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress
- China: A Preliminary Reconcilication of Official and CIA National Product Data by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, December 1979., 219; 9 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER M 79-10690.; Access Points: China
- China: International Trade, 1976-77. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, November 1977., 220; 18 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 77-10674.; Access Points: China
- Influence of Agrotechnology And Geoclimate on Grain Yield Potential in the USSR. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, May 1978., 221; 10 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 78-10058.; Access Points: Russia
- China: In Pursuit of Economic Modernization. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, December 1978., 222; 17 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 89-10680.; Access Points: China
- China: International Trade 1977-78. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, December 1978., 223; 23 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 78-10721.; Access Points: China
- China: Economic Indicators. A Reference Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, December 1978., 224; 50 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 78-10750.; Map. Peoples Republic of China. Petroleum Industry.; Access Points: China
- China: Agriculture in 1978. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, April 1979., 225; 15 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 79-10206.; Access Points: China
- China; The Steel Industry In the 1970's and 1980's. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, May 1979., 226; 12 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 79-10245.; Access Points: China
- China: International Trade Quarterly Review Third Quarter, 1979. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, February 1980., 227; 9 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER CIT 80-002.; Access Points: China
- Electric Power for China's Modernization: The Hydroelectic Option. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, May 1980., 228; 25 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 80-10089U.; Map. China: Hydroelectic Power Plants.; Access Points: China
- China: International Trade Quarterly Review Second Quarter, 1979. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, January 1980., 229; 30 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER CIT 80-001.; Access Points: China
- China: International Trade Quarterly Review Fourth Quarter, 1979. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, May 1980., 230; 32 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER CIT 80-003.; Access Points: China
- China: The Continuing Search for a Modernization Strategy. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, April 1980., 231; 21 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 80-10248.; Access Points: China
- China: International Trade Fourth Quarter, 1980. A Research Paper by National Foreign Assissment Center. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, May 1981., 232; 30 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER CIT 81-003.; Access Points: China
- Agriculture Situation. Review of 1978 and Outlook for 1979. People's Republic of China by United States.Department of Agriculture. Washington, D.C.: United States. Department of Agriculture, June 1979., 233; 38 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Supplement 6 to WAS 18.; Editor CharlesY. Liu with various contributors.; Access Points: China
- Agriculture Situation. Review of 1977 and Outlook for 1978. People's Republic of China by United States.Department of Agriculture. Washington, D.C.: United States. Department of Agriculture, May 1978., 234; 36 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Supplement 6 to WAS 15.; Editor CharlesY. Liu with various contributors.; Access Points: China
- Agriculture Situation. Review of 1974 and Outlook for 1975. People's Republic of China by United States.Department of Agriculture. Washington, D.C.: United States. Department of Agriculture, September 1975., 235; 30 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Foreign Agricultural Economic Report No. 111.; Editor CharlesY. Liu with various contributors.; Access Points: China
- River and Coastal Junks in China's Commerce by Herold J. Wiens. Economic Geography, Vol. 31, No. 3,, July 1955., 236; Pages 248-264; Format: Textual Material; Reprint.; Access Points: China
- China's Economy and Foreign Trade, 1978-79 by United States. Department of Agriculture. Washington, D.C.: United States. Department of Commerce, September 1979., 237; 27 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Written by Nai-Ruenn Chen.; Access Points: China
- The Chinese Economy and Foreign Trade Perspective-1976 by United States Department of Commerce. Washington, D.C.: United States. Department of Commerce, June 1979., 238; 57 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Prepared under Supervision of William C. Clarke.; Access Points: China
- Seven Articles on Land Reform.[Asia] by Asian Studies Center. Michigan State University. East Lansing, MI: Asian Studies Center. Michigan State University, June 1965., 239; 80 Pages; Format: Textual Material; William D. Ross, Director, Asian Studies Center.; Access Points: Asia
- The Rise of the Modern Chinese Business Class by Marion J. Levy, Jr. and Shih Kuo-Heng. New York, N.Y.: Institute of Pacific Relations, 1949., 240; 64 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Essays by Marion J. Levy, Jr. and Shih Kuo-Heng.; Access Points: China
- The Rise of the New People's Democratic Economy 1927-1937 by Institue of Advance Projects. Honolulu, HI: Institue of Advance Projects, 1969., 241; 76 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Lectures by Chung-kuo,Hupei University, China.; Translated by William W.L. Wan.; Access Points: China
- Growth of the Construction Industry in Communist China by Kang Chao. Ann Arbor, MI: Center for Chinese Studies, University of Michigan., 242; 17 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Extract from The China Quarterly, Ilford House, London England. Apr.-June, 1965. Pages 125-142.; Access Points: China
- The Budgetary System of the People's Republic of China: A Preliminary Survey by Ching-Wen Kwang. Berkeley, CA: Committee on the Economy of China, Berkeley, CA, 1964., 243; 33 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Reprint from Public Finance, Universitad des Saarlandes, Saabrucken 15, Germand Vol.XV111, No.3-4 1963. Pages 253-286; Access Points: China
- The Terms of Sino-Soviet Trade by Feng-Hwa Mah. Seattle, WA: Far Eastern and Russian Insitute, Univ. of WA, Seattle WA., 244; 17 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Reprint from The China Quarterly, The Eastern Press, Ltd. London, England. Jan.-March, 1964. Pages 174-191.; Access Points: China
- A Study of the Rouble-Yuan Exchange Rate by Kang Chao and Feng-Hwa Mah. Seattle, WA: Far Eastern and Russian Insitute, Univ. of WA, Seattle WA., 245; 12 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Reprint from The China Quarterly, The Eastern Press, Ltd. London, England. Jan.-March, 1964. Pages 192-204.; Access Points: China
- A Note on the Choice of Technology in China by Shigeru Ishikawa. The Journal of Development Studies, Vol. 9 No. 1, October 1972., 246; Pages 161-186; Format: Textual Material; Reprint from Frank Case & Co. Ltd., London, England.; Access Points: China
- The Manchurian Iron and Steel Industry and its Resource Base by Allan Rodgers. The Geographical Review, Vol. 38, No. 1, January 1948., 247; Pages 41-54; Format: Textual Material; Reprint.; Access Points: Manchuria
- Birth Control in China by Michael Freeberne. Population Studies, Vol. 18, No. 1, p. 5, July 1964., 248; Pages 5-16; Format: Textual Material; Reprint.; Access Points: China
- Elements of Instability in the Current Japanese Land Tenure System by John D. Eyre. Land Economics, Vol. 28, No. 3, August 1952., 249; Pages 193-202; Format: Textual Material; Reprint.; Access Points: Japan
- The Changing Role of the Former Japanese Landlord by John D. Eyre. Land Economics, Vol. 31, No. 1, February 1955., 250; Pages 36-46; Format: Textual Material; Reprint.; Access Points: Japan
- China's National Railways by H. J. von Lochow. Peiping, China: H. J. von Lochow, 1948., 251; 162 Pages; Format: Textual Material; LOC call number HE3285.L6.; Access Points: China
- Cornell Workshop on Agricultural and Rural Development in the Republic of China by The Center for the Analysis of World Food Issues. Ithaca, NY: Cornell University, May 17-19, 1979., 252; 58 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Access Points: China
- The size, composition, and growth of the population of mainland China by John S. Aird. Washington, D.C.: U. S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census, 1961, 1961., 253; 100 Pages; Format: Textual Material; LOC call number HB3637.A55 1973.; Access Points: China
- Anshan Steel Factory in Communist China by Cheng, Chu-yuan. Kowloon, H.K.: Union Research Institute, 1955., 254; 88 Pages; Format: Textual Material; LOC call number HD9526.C64 A53.; Access Points: China
- Economic Planning in Communist China by Hsia, Ronald. Cambridge, MA: Center for International Studies, MIT, 1953., 255; 71 Pages; Format: Textual Material; LOC call number HC427.H68.; Access Points: China
- China: Area, Administration and National Building by Whitney, Joseph B.R.. Chicago, IL: University of Chicago.Dept. of Geography, 1970., 256; 198 Pages; Format: Textual Material; LOC call number DS706.5.W48.; Access Points: China
- Cities of Mainland China: 1953 and 1958 by Ullman, Morris Benjamin. Washington, D.C.: Foreign Manpower Research Office, 1961., 257; 46 Pages; Format: Textual Material; LOC call number HC331.U52 no.59.; Access Points: China
- Communist China Map Folio by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington,D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency. Directorate of Intelligence, October 1967., 258; 40 Pages 440 x 550 cm.; various; Conic Egual Area; Format: Atlas; Access Points: China
- Communist China Administrative Atlas by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington,D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, March 1969., 259; 34 Pages 440 x 550 cm.; various; Format: Atlas; Access Points: China
- Economic atlas of Szechuan--Shuo ming. Ssu-ch'uan ching chi ti t'u chi. by Pei-ch'ei, Chung-kuo ti li yen chiu so, Min-kuo 35. 1946., 260; Format: Atlas; LOC call number G2308.S9 C56 1946. Copy 1; Access Points: China
- Temperature and River Basins in China, 261; 12 Charts 240 x 180 cm; Format: Chart; Access Points: China
- East Asia by Goode Base Map Series. Chicago, IL: Dept. Of Geography, University of Chicago, 1963., 262; 1 map 430 x 280 cm.; Conic Projection; Format: Map; Henry M. Leppard, Editor; Access Points: China
- [Circular Bar Graphs for Cities in China showing Months, Days and unknown markings], 263; 28 charts 280 x 220 cm; Format: Chart; Temperature[?], Rainfall[?].; Access Points: Aisa
- The Geography of Kapingamarangi Atoll in the Eastern Carolines by Herold J. Wiens. New Haven, CN: Yale University, New Haven, CN, June 1955., 264; 99 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Scientific Investigations in Micronesia.; Pacific Science Board and the National Research Council.; Access Points: China